// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A watch gain 8 seconds in 4 minutes and was set right at 4 AM. What time will it show at 11 PM on the same day?",
    answer: "11:38",
    options: [
      "11:38",
      "11:08",
      "11:28",
      "11:18"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Pick the odd one out",
    answer: "Weeder",
    options: [
      "Weeder",
      "Spader",
      "Twig",
      "Shovel"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:" Manager : Assistant :: Doctor : ?",
    answer: "Nurse",
    options: [
      "Chemist",
      "doctor",
      "Nurse",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Ducks : Quack :: Cow : ?",
    answer: "Moo",
    options: [
      "Moo",
      "woo",
      "yoo",
      "Both A and C"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 5,
    question: " 19, 25, 32, 40, ?, 59",
    answer: "49",
    options: [
      "49",
      "39",
      "46",
      "34"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Read the following information carefully and answer the question below. 1. J + K means J is the son of K 2. J - K means J is the wife of K 3. J x K means J is the brother of K 4. J ÷ K means J is the mother of K 5. J = K means J is the sister of KWhat does A x B ÷ C mean?",
    answer: "A is the uncle of C",
    options: [
      "A is the father of C",
      "A is the father of C",
      "A is the father of C",
      "Both B and C"
    ]
  }
,

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Read the following information carefully and answer the questions below.1. P x Q means P is the father of Q 2. P - Q means P is the sister of Q3. P + Q means P is the mother of Q 4. P ÷ Q means P is the brother of QWhich of the following represents ‘R is niece of M’?",
    answer: "M – J + R – N",
    options: [
      "M – J + R – N",
      "M – K x T - R",
      " M + K x T - R",
      "M – K x T *R"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Joe is walking towards North for 15 miles, turns left and walks another 10 miles. He then turns right and walks 10 miles. Now, he again turns right and walks 30 miles. Which direction is he from Starting point? ",
    answer: "North-East",
    options: [
      "All of the above",
      "North-East",
      "North-West",
      "North-South"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Joe is facing towards South and turns 45° anti-clockwise. He turns again 180° in anti-clockwise direction. Now, he turns 270° clockwise. Which direction is he facing?",
    answer: "South-West",
    options: [
      "South-West",
      "South",
      "South-east",
      "North"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Pick the odd one out",
    answer: "Cow",
    options: [
      "Cow",
      "Cat",
      "Tiger",
      "Panther"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Pick the odd one out",
    answer: "Weeder",
    options: [
      "Weeder",
      "Spader",
      "Twig",
      "Shovel"
    ]
  }

 

  
  
    
];